{"__cache./api/resource/task/40186/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40186,"taskName":"Upholstery and Furniture - Clean","taskDescription":"Clean Upholstery and Furniture","xmTaskDescriptor":"Furniture Upholstery Cleaning Services","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":91,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Clean moisture low cleaners berber","textMessagingName":"Clean Upholstery","rolloverLongDesc":"Typically performed in the home, furniture fabrics can be cleaned by any one of a variety of methods including steam cleaning, drycleaning \u0026 shampooing. May include application of fabric protection sprays such as Scotchguard.","rolloverShortDesc":"Clean upholstery \u0026 furniture in the home.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Clean Upholstery and Furniture.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Furniture Cleaners | Upholstery Cleaners","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":10,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":5,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Clean Upholstery \u0026 Furniture","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Upholstery and Furniture - Clean","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Upholstery \u0026 Furniture Cleaning Project","urlName":"Upholstery-and-Furniture-Clean","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Upholstery Cleaning Services - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Furniture Cleaning","searchKeywords":"Clean,moisture,low,cleaners,berber,fabric,Upholstery,carpet,cleaning,cleaner,Furniture,reupholster, reupholstery","emcCategoryOid":-12011,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":494,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Furniture Upholstery Cleaning Services","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40186/":{"taskOID":40186,"originalTaskOID":40186,"setID":494,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":4342,"questionDisplayText":"Furnishings to be Cleaned","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Which furnishings do you want to have cleaned? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5846,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Sofa","answerDisplayText":"Sofa","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3678,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Loveseat","answerDisplayText":"Loveseat","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":840,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Armchair","answerDisplayText":"Armchair","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5065,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Recliner","answerDisplayText":"Recliner","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4466,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Ottoman","answerDisplayText":"Ottoman","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6774,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Walls","answerDisplayText":"Walls","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502545,"questionDisplayText":"Type of material","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of material do you want cleaned?","shortQuestionText":"What type of material do you want cleaned?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":203424,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Fabric","answerDisplayText":"Fabric","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3524,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Leather","answerDisplayText":"Leather","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4345,"questionDisplayText":"When last cleaned","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"When was it last cleaned?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3546,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Less than 2 years ago","answerDisplayText":"Less than 2 years ago","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":401,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"2-5 years ago","answerDisplayText":"2-5 years ago","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3933,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"More than 5 years ago","answerDisplayText":"More than 5 years ago","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4129,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Never","answerDisplayText":"Never","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4344,"questionDisplayText":"Furniture Age","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How old is the furniture?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3545,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Less than 2 years","answerDisplayText":"Less than 2 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":400,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"2-5 years","answerDisplayText":"2-5 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":519,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"5-10 years","answerDisplayText":"5-10 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4351,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Older than 10 years","answerDisplayText":"Older than 10 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":4342,"questionDisplayText":"Furnishings to be Cleaned","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Which furnishings do you want to have cleaned? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5846,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Sofa","answerDisplayText":"Sofa","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3678,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Loveseat","answerDisplayText":"Loveseat","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":840,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Armchair","answerDisplayText":"Armchair","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5065,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Recliner","answerDisplayText":"Recliner","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4466,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Ottoman","answerDisplayText":"Ottoman","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6774,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Walls","answerDisplayText":"Walls","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5846,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Sofa","answerDisplayText":"Sofa","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3678,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Loveseat","answerDisplayText":"Loveseat","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":840,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Armchair","answerDisplayText":"Armchair","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5065,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Recliner","answerDisplayText":"Recliner","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4466,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Ottoman","answerDisplayText":"Ottoman","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6774,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Walls","answerDisplayText":"Walls","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502545,"questionDisplayText":"Type of material","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of material do you want cleaned?","shortQuestionText":"What type of material do you want cleaned?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":203424,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Fabric","answerDisplayText":"Fabric","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3524,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Leather","answerDisplayText":"Leather","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":203424,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Fabric","answerDisplayText":"Fabric","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3524,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Leather","answerDisplayText":"Leather","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4345,"questionDisplayText":"When last cleaned","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"When was it last cleaned?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3546,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Less than 2 years ago","answerDisplayText":"Less than 2 years ago","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":401,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"2-5 years ago","answerDisplayText":"2-5 years ago","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3933,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"More than 5 years ago","answerDisplayText":"More than 5 years ago","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4129,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Never","answerDisplayText":"Never","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":3546,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Less than 2 years ago","answerDisplayText":"Less than 2 years ago","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":401,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"2-5 years ago","answerDisplayText":"2-5 years ago","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3933,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"More than 5 years ago","answerDisplayText":"More than 5 years ago","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4129,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Never","answerDisplayText":"Never","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4344,"questionDisplayText":"Furniture Age","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How old is the furniture?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3545,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Less than 2 years","answerDisplayText":"Less than 2 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":400,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"2-5 years","answerDisplayText":"2-5 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":519,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"5-10 years","answerDisplayText":"5-10 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4351,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Older than 10 years","answerDisplayText":"Older than 10 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":3545,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Less than 2 years","answerDisplayText":"Less than 2 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":400,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"2-5 years","answerDisplayText":"2-5 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":519,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"5-10 years","answerDisplayText":"5-10 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4351,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Older than 10 years","answerDisplayText":"Older than 10 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]}}